

Profile

I am a passionate programmer with experience developing WordPress websites. My background ranges from creating small websites to managing and developing complex online stores with Woocommerce, third-party integrations and advanced customization.

My focus on staying up to date with the latest trends and tools has allowed me to constantly improve my work and offer innovative solutions to technical challenges.

Employment History

Web Developer, Enigma Diseño, Puebla

NOVEMBER 2018 - JANUARY 2022

Website development with Wordpress, e-commerce development with Woocommerce, Front End Solutions application with Javascript or jQuery, portfolio system development for the currently functional agency, repository management, hosting and certificate management.

Technologies: Wordpress, Woocommerce, HTML5, CSS, Sass, PHP, ACF, Javascript, Git, Adobe Illustrator.

Modality: Hybrid.

Programmer Consultant | Fullstack Web developer, LK Asociados, Puebla

FEBRUARY 2022 - MAY 2023

Development of custom sites and themes with Wordpress, development of e-commerce with WooCommerce, construction of sites with Divi and Elementor, SEO audits, website optimization, project management, management of hosting and certificates, presentations with clients, improvement of internal processes . Technologies: Wordpress, Woocommerce, Divi, Elementor, HTML5 Css, Sass, PHP, Javascript, CPANEL, GoDaddy

Mode: Remote.

Fullstack Wordpress Developer, Mijo! Brands, Cancún

JUNE 2023 - PRESENT

Development of real estate sites with Wordpress and Woocommerce through the creation and customization of Gutenberg blocks, implementation and customization of tools such as FlexMLS and Motorpress, Maintenance and optimization of Websites, development of plugins for Wordpress, repository management, client presentations.

Technologies: Wordpress, Woocommerce, Flexmls, Motorpress, Gutenberg blocks, ACF postCss, Javascript, PHP, LaravelMix, Node.js, Git, BitBucket.

Mode: Remote.

Education

Graduate, Instituto de Estudios Universitarios, Puebla

AUGUST 2015 - NOVEMBER 2018

Graduated with a Bachelor's degree in Information Systems and Technology Engineering.

References

Details

Cancún México

2212103024

underscoreyair@gmail.com

Links

Linkedin

Skills

Logical thinking

Fast learning

Independence

Adaptability

Team worker

Perseverance

Languages

Inglés

Español

Hobbies

Reading, Chess, Music

Alfredo López Sherman from Enigma Diseño - Diseñador Senior 5212225640327

Antonio Barbizan from LK Asociados - Estratega Digital 5212221431277

Juan Gonzáles Medina from Mijo!Brands - Wordpress Developer juanglzm24@gmail | 6861879760